Shown on screen right now is what you
can typically expect a Coyo 2 text to
image workflow to look like. And on our
canvas now is what you might expect a
Coyo 2 image to image workflow to look
like. And if we add both of those
workflows together, so you're not
hopping from workflow to workflow, this
is what you might expect that to look
like. As you can see, this is very
crowded and disastrous situation. But
what if I told you guys that I came up
with solution that takes all of this
and turns it into something that looks
like this. Hanging out on the canvas
right now is the Coyo 2 one node Comfy
UI integration in which I have created
for you guys. Essentially, what this is
is both of those workflows crammed into
one super intuitive UI that is extremely
easy to navigate and makes your Coyo 2
image generation pipeline extremely easy
to manage. This is going to be
completely free to everyone soon in the
near future, but you can get your hands
on it right now and I'll tell you
exactly how a little bit later. So here
is an example of a generation that we
have just done. We can see the reference
photo here and then we have just
replaced that person in the reference
photo with our Laura. It looks great.
Everything came out good. I like how it
slightly regenerates the background and
surroundings as well as the outfit and
clothing and so on. It gives your images
some sort of originality. You're not
just taking somebody's photo and just
completely replacing the person. All
right, here we have another example.
Yeah guys, this is the Coyo 2 one node
that I built. If this looks like
something that interests you, right now
this is exclusive to Patreon supporters.
So if you go over to my Patreon, the
link is in the description and
subscribe, it's yours today. Again, I
really appreciate the support that you
guys provide through Patreon. It helps
me out a ton and it keeps me making
these videos. If